If you love him,
use your monstrous power.
OUTER SCIENCE
CONCEAL
STEAL
DECEIVE
CAPTIVATE
OPEN
XX
FOCUS
WAKE
MEET
I don't care for a world
without all of you...
A life lived puny
and miserably;
once dead, should it not
knock at the door?
The little
master watches
attentively;
"What loathsome tales."
A large-reaching throat
and body, as if dissolving
a dead heart,
slowly gulp down life,
gouging out eyes...
Say, you wished for it too, didn't you?
In that moment I glared at you...
Such tragic souls
are my favorite meal...
Welcome to my womb,
love
and ego's
love and ego's final destination
You too will soon be born anew;
is it not
fantastic,
is it not fantastic, to be like a monster?
"Oh, god, why?", hm?
"I don't want it,"
"I don't want it," you cry
Merely accept it - this is fate!
The next, next, next master,
I eagerly await...
Myths, lives, the
destinies of people,
even carelessly
falling in love...
The quiet
snake
laughs
loud:
"Such foolish things."
Ahh, I just can't
seem to get enough;
putting down
darkened hearts,
possessing their little lives,
embedding in their eyes...
Ahh, it dwells in you, does it not?
The ability of meeting eyes...
The fate of unifying eyes...
Indeed, in this tragedy,
you are the "queen"...
Lives, give praise;
as love
and ego
as love and ego press hands together,
the shaking days begin to crumble,
and toward
the initial
tragedy,
and toward the initial tragedy, they pace together...
"Give it back," you lament
"I've had enough," you wail
You think I care? That is fate!
This terrible, brittle, puny story
is the real thing!
How idiotic
are your lives...
Time and time again, you resist,
beginning to revert to the same old story,
recklessly, uncouthly,
crying,
weeping,
howling,
writhing...
Ahh, what unsightly lives!
Before you even ask "Why?"
You demand too much - serve for your crime!
A hollow miracle
snaps and crumbles...
"I, I don't even care anymore";
again and again,
you just sit and cry
As even the end immediately fades,
The next, the next, the next to come,
at the next, and the next day,
and the next,
I'll still sneer...